https://www.utilityfasteners.co.uk/main/company_information/legal_info/gdpr:-data-privacy-notice

Cookies are used on our website. Please click here for more information.
Toggle navigation
HEXAGON BOLTINGHexagon Bolts Steel BZPHexagon Bolts Self ColourHexagon Bolts A2Hexagon Bolts A4Hexagon Set Screws Steel BZPHexagon Set Screws Steel Self ColourHexagon Set Screws A2Hexagon Set Screws A4Pre-Load Bolt AssembliesCoach Bolts BZPCoach Screws BZPUNC Hexagon Bolts BZPUNC Hexagon Bolts Self ColourUNC Hexagon Set Screws BZPUNC Hexagon Set Screws S/ColourHexagon Flange Bolts BZPSOCKET SCREW PRODUCTSSocket Cap Screw BZPSocket Cap Screw PlainSocket Cap Screw A2Socket Cap Screw A4Socket Cap Screw Fully Threaded BZPButton Socket Screw BZPButton Socket Screw PlainButton Socket Screw A2Button Socket Screw A4Countersunk Socket Screw BZPCountersunk Socket Screw PlainCountersunk Socket Screw A2Countersunk Socket Screw A4Socket Set Screw Cup Point BZPSocket Set Screw Cup Point PlainSocket Set Screw Cup Point A2Socket Set Screw Cup Point A4Hexagon Socket Shoulder ScrewsNUTSHexagon Full Nut 8.8 Steel and Steel Bright Zinc PlatedHexagon Thin Nuts Steel Bright Zinc PlatedHexagon Nylock NutsHexagon Flanged Nut (Serrated)Hexagon Domed NutsWing Nut (American) TypeAll Metal Locking NutsShear NutsHexagonal Stud Connector NutsPronged Tee Nuts Steel Bright Zinc PlatedNut & Bolt Cover CapsBLIND RIVETS, RIVET NUTS & TOOLINGDome Head Blind RivetsDome Head Aluminium/Steel RivetsDome Head Steel/Steel RivetsDome Head Stainless/Stainless RivetsCountersunk RivetsAluminium/SteelSteel/SteelStainless/StainlessLarge Flange RivetsAluminium/SteelSteel/SteelStainless/StainlessMulti-Grip RivetsDome Head Aluminium/Steel Multigrip RivetDome Head Steel/Steel Multigrip RivetDome Head Stainless/Stainless RivetLarge Flange Aluminium/Steel Multigrip RivetSealed RivetsCountersunk Aluminium/Steel Sealed RivetDome Head Aluminium/Steel RivetDome Head Steel/Steel RivetDome Head Aluminium/Stainless RivetDome Head Stainless/Stainless RivetGrooved RivetsPeeled RivetsDome Head Aluminium/Steel Peeled RIvetDome Head Aluminium/Aluminium Triform RivetLarge Flange Aluminium/Stainless Hammerdrive RivetStructural RivetsDome Head Structural Steel RivetsCountersunk Head Structural Steel RivetsDome Head Structural Aluminium RivetsCountersunk Head Structural Aluminium RivetsDome Head Structural Stainless Steel RivetsCountersunk Head Structural Stainless Steel RivetsDome Head Aluminium/Aluminium Triform Washered RivetsRivet NutsReduced Head Knurled Metric Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPReduced Head Knurled Imperial Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPCountersunk Head Knurled Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPFlat Head Knurled Metric Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPReduced Head Half Hexagon Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPReduced Head Full Hexagon Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPFlat Head Half Hex Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPFlat Head Full Hexagon Body Rivet Nut Steel BZPReduced Head Knurled Metric Body Rivet Nut Stainless SteelCountersunk Head Knurled Body Rivet Nut Stainless SteelFlat Head Knurled Metric Body Rivet Nut Stainless SteelReduced Head Half Hexagon Body Rivet Nut Stainless SteelRivet Setting ToolsRivet Nut Setting ToolsCONSTRUCTION FIXINGSBonded Anchors and ResinsResins for Bonded AnchorsSpin in Resin CapsulesHammer in Resin CapsulesPolyester ResinsVinylester ResinsEpoxy ResinsChemical Anchor StudsChemical Anchor Studs Hex Head Grade 5.8 Zinc PlatedChemical Anchor Studs Hex Head Grade 8.8 Zinc PlatedChemical Anchor Studs Hex Head Grade 5.8 Hot Dipped GalvanisedChemical Anchor Studs Hex Head Grade A2/304Chemical Anchor Studs Hex Head Grade A4/316Chemical Anchor Studs Flat Head Grade 5.8 Zinc PlatedChemical Anchor Studs Flat Head Grade A4/316Internal Threaded SocketsInternal Threaded Sockets Zinc PlatedInternal Threaded Sockets Stainless Steel Grade A2Internal Threaded Sockets Stainless Steel Grade A4Dispenser Guns and Accessories for Bonded AnchorsInjection Resin AccessoriesHole Cleaning Brushes & PumpsMechanical AnchorsThroughbolts / Wedge AnchorsThroughbolts Zinc PlatedAnker BoltsHexagon Flange Head Anker Bolt BZPCountersunk Torx Drive Anker Bolts BZPHexagon Head Anker Bolt BZPSleeve AnchorsSleeve Anchor - Hexagon Nut Zinc PlatedSleeve Anchor - Hexagon Bolt Zinc PlatedSleeve Anchor - Countersunk Head Zinc PlatedSleeve Anchor - Hexagon Nut Stainless Steel A4-316Shield AnchorsShield Only BZPShield Anchor Projecting Stud BZPShield Anchor - Loose Bolt BZPBlind BoltsDrop In AnchorsDrop In AnchorLipped Drop in AnchorDrop In Anchor Stainless Steel A4Drop In Anchor Setting PunchesLightweight FixingsHammerfix Screw Steel BZPHammerfix Screw Stainless Steel A2Nylon Frame FixingCountersunk Nylon Frame Fixing - ETAG020-01Hexagonal Head Nylon Frame Fixing - ETAG020-01Countersunk Nylon Frame Fixing -Stainless Steel A4 -
ETAG020-01Plastic Plugs - StandardNylon Wall PlugsStudding, Allthreads and Engineering Studs.Studding 1 Meter Grade 4.8 & 8.8 Self Colour and BZPStudding 3 Meter Grade 4.8 & 8.8 Self Colour and BZPStudding 1 Meter Stainless Steel Grade A2 and A4Studding 3 Meter Stainless Steel Grade A2 & A4MoreSCREW PRODUCTSMachine ScrewsCountersunk Slotted Machine Screws BZPCountersunk Pozi Machine Screws BZPPan Slotted Machine Screws BZPPan Pozi Machine Screws BZPRoofing Bolt & Square Pressed Nut BZPSelf Tapping ScrewsPan Head Pozi Self Tapping Screws Type F BZPCountersunk Pozi, Type F(B) Self Tapping Screw BZPHexagon Head Self Tapping Screw BZPCountersunk Pozi Self Tapping Screws AB BZPPan Pozi Self Tapping Screws AB BZPFlanged Pozi Self Tapping Screw AB BZPSelf Drill ScrewsHexagon Head Self Drill Screw Zinc PlatedHex Head Self Drill Screw Light Section Steel BZPHex Head Self Drill Screw Heavy Section Steel BZPHex Head Stitcher Screws BZPPan Head Phillips Self Drill Screw BZPTimber to Steel Light SectionTimber to Steel Heavy SectionCountersunk Head Self Drill ScrewWafer Head Drill Screw BZPWood ScrewsCountersunk Pozi Twin Thread Woodscrews BZPRound Head Pozi Twin Thread Woodscrews BZPRound Head Pozi Twin Thread Woodscrews Black JapanSolo Woodscrews - YellowClassic Multi-Purpose Chipboard ScrewsC2 Multi-Purpose Advanced ScrewsDrywall ScrewsDrywall Fine Thread Screws Black Phos.Drywall Fine Thread Screws BZPDrywall Self Drill Screws BZPSecurity Screws2-Hole ScrewsCountersunk 2-Hole Self Tapping Screw AB A2Pan Head 2-Hole Self Tapping Screw AB A2Countersunk 2-Hole Machine Screw A2Pan Head 2-Hole Machine Screw A22-Hole Security Screw Insert BitsPin Hex ScrewsCountersunk Pin Hex Self Tapping Screw AB A2Pan Head Pin Hex Self Tapping Screw AB A2Countersunk Pin Hex Machine Screw A2Pan Head Pin Hex Machine Screw A2Pin Hex Security Screw Insert Bits6-Lobe PinCountersunk 6-Lobe Pin Self Tapper AB A2Button Head 6-Lobe Pin Self Tapper AB A2Countersunk 6-Lobe Pin Machine Screw A2Button Head 6-Lobe Pin Machine Screw A26-Lobe Pin Security Screw Insert BitsClutch HeadCountersunk Clutch Head Twin Thread Woodscrew BZPCountersunk Clutch Head Self Tapping Screw AB A2Round Clutch Head Self Tapping Screw AB A2Round Clutch Head Machine Screw A2Plasfast ® 30° Thread-Forming ScrewsCountersunk Head Plasfast ® 30°Pan Head Plasfast ® 30°Flange Head Plasfast ® 30°Plasfast ® 60° Thread-Forming ScrewsCountersunk Head Plasfast ® 60°Pan Head Plasfast ® 60°Tritap® Thread-Forming ScrewsCountersunk Head CR Z Tritap® ScrewPan Head CR Z Tritap® ScrewIndented Hexagon Washer Head Tritap® ScrewSocket Cap Head Tritap® ScrewCountersunk Head Torx DriveTritap® ScrewPan Head Torx Drive Tritap® ScrewPOWER TOOLSDrills 110v 240v and CordlessPercussion Drills 110v 240v and CordlessSDS Hammer Drills 110v 240v and CordlessScrewdrivers 110v 240v and CordlessGrinders 110v 240v and CordlessMetalworking Tools 110v 240v and Cordless CORDLESSMAKITABOSCH BLUEDEWALTHITACHI110v/240vMAKITAPOWER TOOL ACCESSORIESHSS JOBBER DRILL BITSHSS STUB DRILL BITSHSS LONG SERIES DRILL BITSHSS SUPERCOBALT DRILL BITSBLACKSMITHS DRILL BITSSTRAIGHT SHANK MASONARY DRILL BITSSDS PLUS DRILL BITSSDS PLUS HIGH PERFORMANCE DRILL BITSCARBON STEEL TAP SETS - STD METRIC COARSEHIGH SPEED STEEL TAP SETS - STD METRIC COARSEWASHERSFlat Washer Form AFlat Washer Form BFlat Washer Form CRepair WashersSquare Section Spring WashersLock Washers Internal TeethLock Washers External TeethStarlock WashersABRASIVES AND CUTTING PRODUCTSCutting DiscsGrinding DiscsAbrasive Mop DiscsAbrasive DiscsCLIPS, TIES AND PINSCONSUMABLESAssortment BoxesAction Can Products
×
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Enter your email address below
We will never share your details with a third party.
See our privacy policy
Close
×Close
Log in
×Close
Your basket
Your basket is empty
Shop Now >>
Utility Fasteners Limited ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of use - https://www.utilityfasteners.co.uk/super/company_info/edit/6 and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
The rules on processing of personal data are set out in the General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”).
1.      Definitions
Data controller - A controller determines the purposes and means of processing personal data.
Data processor - A processor is responsible for processing personal data on behalf of a controller.
Data subject – Natural person
Categories of data: Personal data and special categories of personal data
Personal data - The GDPR applies to ‘personal data’ meaning any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier (as explained in Article 6 of GDPR). For example, name, passport number, home address or private email address. Online identifiers include IP addresses and cookies.
Special categories personal data - The GDPR refers to sensitive personal data as ‘special categories of personal data’ (as explained in Article 9 of GDPR). The special categories specifically include genetic data, and biometric data where processed to uniquely identify an individual. Other examples include racial and ethnic origin, sexual orientation, health data, trade union membership, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs.
Processing - means any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.
Third party - means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or body other than the data subject, controller, processor and persons who, under the direct authority of the controller or processor, are authorised to process personal data.
2.      Who are we?
Utility Fasteners Limited is the data controller. This means we decide how your personal data is processed and for what purposes. Our contact details are:
Utility Fasteners Limited
Unit 4 Bellman Gate
Holcot Lane
Sywell
Northamptonshire
NN6 0BL
For all data matters please contact our data representative on info@utilityfasteners.co.uk or telephone 01604 671038
3.      The purpose(s) of processing your personal data
We use your personal data for the following purposes:
You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our site www.utilityfasteners.co.uk  (our site) or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when you register to use our site, subscribe to our service, search for a product, place an order on our site, participate in discussion boards or other social media functions on our site, enter a competition, promotion or survey, and when you report a problem with our site.
To inform individuals of news, events or activities;
To maintain our own accounts and records;
To manage our employees.
4.      The categories of personal data concerned
With reference to the categories of personal data described in the definitions section, we process the following categories of your data:
Personal data
The personal data you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information.
5.      What is our legal basis for processing your personal data?
a)     Personal data (article 6 of GDPR)
Our lawful basis for processing your general personal data:
Processing necessary for the performance of a contract with the data subject or to take steps to enter into a contract
To facilitate the sale and delivery of;
Industrial Fasteners and Construction Fixings, Tooling and Workshop Consumable Items.
b)     Special categories of personal data (article 9 of GDPR)
Our lawful basis for processing your special categories of data:
We do not collect special categories of data (i.e. sensitive personal data).
6.     Sharing your personal data
We make sure that access to your personal information is limited to those of our staff who need it, and that all staff understand how and why we protect your personal information.
Your personal data will be treated as strictly confidential and will be shared only with other companies that we work with in order to fulfil our contract of sale with you, the buyer, such as logistics, freight and delivery companies and payment processing organisations.
Please note that we will never sell your personal information to any body or organisation, and we will only share it as outlined in this privacy policy.
7.     How long do we keep your personal data?
We only keep your personal information for as long as we need to, to be able to use it for the reasons given in this privacy policy, and for as long as we are required to keep it by law. The actual period for which we store your personal information will vary depending on the type of personal information and how it is used.
8.      Providing us with your personal data
We require your personal data as it is a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
Without your personal data we will be unable to provide the goods as ordered.
9.      Your rights and your personal data
Unless subject to an exemption under the GDPR, you have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
The right to request a copy of the personal data which we hold about you;
The right to request that we correct any personal data if it is found to be inaccurate or out of date;
The right to request your personal data is erased where it is no longer necessary to retain such data;
The right to request that we provide you with your personal data and where possible, to transmit that data directly to another data controller, (known as the right to data portability), (where applicable i.e. where the processing is based on consent or is necessary for the performance of a contract with the data subject and where the data controller processes the data by automated means);
The right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or processing of your personal data, to request a restriction is placed on further processing;
The right to object to the processing of personal data, (where applicable i.e. where processing is based on legitimate interests (or the performance of a task in the public interest/exercise of official authority); direct marketing and processing for the purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics).
10.     Transfer of Data Abroad
We do not transfer personal data outside the eea.
11.     Automated Decision Making
WE DO NOT USE ANY FORM OF AUTOMATED DECISION MAKING IN OUR BUSINESS.
12.      Further processing
If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, not covered by this Data Privacy Notice, then we will provide you with a new notice explaining this new use prior to commencing the processing and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions.
13.      Changes to our privacy policy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
14.      How to make a complaint
To exercise all relevant rights, queries or complaints please in the first instance contact our Data Representative on info@utilityfasteners.co.uk
If this does not resolve your complaint to your satisfaction, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioners Office on 03031231113 or via email https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email/ or at the Information Commissioner's Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire, SK9 5AF, England.
Last updated September 2020.
Contact us
Address :
Design by - Sharp-ax Computer Systems Ltd.
Back to Top
